Guide to the William J. Roege Photograph Collection 1910-1937, undated PR 181
New-York Historical Society
William J. Roege Photograph Collection
1910-1937, undated
New-York Historical Society
PR 181
7.3 Linear feet (12 boxes)
The collection consists of photographs and negatives by commercial photographer William J. Roege documenting popular New York City buildings, streets and businesses between 1910 and 1937. The William J. Roege Photograph Collection is digitized and available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Provenance
Approximately 500 vintage negatives and corresponding photographic prints by William J. Roege were purchased on March 19, 1940. The vintage prints were dispersed throughout the Geographic File (PR 020); the negatives remain in this collection. Modern contact prints in this collection were produced between 1968 through 1970 by Klein Brothers Studio, New York, under contract with the New-York Historical Society to reformat its oversize glass negatives. The majority of the oversize negatives from which photographic prints were made were destroyed.
Access Restrictions
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Biographical Note
Photographer William J. Roege (1883-1970) worked for commercial photography firms and independently in New York City from at least 1914 through the 1950s, turning his camera toward the businesses and residences of Manhattan and Brooklyn. From at least 1914 through 1923, Roege worked for the firm American Studio at 87 Nassau Street, while making his home in Newark and then Belleville, New Jersey. Photographs within this collection indicate that he was working as a photographer as early as 1910. By 1925, Roege was working at Boyette, the eponymous commercial photography firm owned by Fine Boyette located at 105 West 47th Street, and had moved his residence temporarily to Manhattan. By the 1950s, Roege had moved back to New Jersey, and in 1957 he began using his Belleville address as his sole business address. The business continued to be listed in his name in city directories through the 1970s, although Social Security records indicate that Roege died in December of 1970. Little is known of Roege's life beyond his professional work.
Scope and Content Note
The William J. Roege Photograph Collection spans the period from 1910 through 1935, during the early part of Roege's long career, when he was based in New York. Photographic prints and negatives depict New York City buildings, parks, residences, and street life. The collection is especially rich in views of hotels and restaurants which have largely vanished. Other views include Times Square in the 1910s, Columbus Circle in 1918, and upper Fifth Avenue residences in the 1920s. There are also several rooftop and high-angle views of Manhattan and the Hudson and East Rivers, views of Brooklyn, the New Jersey waterfront, and other nearby locations. It is likely that some of the photographs in this collection were produced in the course of Roege's employment at American Studio and Boyette, both of New York, as several photographs bear Boyette's name in script, together with Roege's signature.
The collection is organized into two series: Photographic Prints; and Negatives. Roege signed most of his images, and sometimes he supplied the date and location. His signature often conforms to the structure depicted; for example, he has signed along the running board of a 1930s automobile, and on the edge of a street curb. Undated photographs can safely be ascribed to the period before 1940, the year the Society acquired this collection. It should be noted that a few of the photographs and negatives are copies of Roege's earlier works, or lithographs, and of other photographers' New York views.
Arrangement
Photographic prints are arranged by subject; negatives are arranged by negative number.
The collection is organized into two series based on format:
Missing Title
Series I: Photographic Prints
Series II: Negatives
Related Material
Nearly 500 vintage prints by Roege, many of which correspond to negatives in this collection, remain dispersed throughout the Geographic File (PR 020). Oversize negatives and modern prints from the William J. Roege Photograph Collection were originally housed with the George P. Hall & Son Photograph Collection; it is possible that a few items by Roege remain in the Hall Collection if they carry no indication of their creator.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital copies are available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Streets -- New York (State) -- New York.; New York (N.Y.) -- Pictorial works.; Architecture, Domestic -- New York (State) -- New York.; Fifth Avenue (New York, N.Y.) -- Pictorial works.; negatives (photographs); Photographic prints.; Hotels -- New York (State) -- New York.; Restaurants -- New York (State) -- New York.; Ocean liners.; Boyette (Firm); Roege, William J., 1893-1970
- Series I: Photographic Prints
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I spans the period from 1910 to ca. 1931 and includes some undated images. The approximately 175 photographic prints in this series are modern 11 x 14 inch silver gelatin contact prints produced by Klein Brothers Studios, New York, between 1968 and 1970 from Roege's vintage negatives. They were made as part of the New-York Historical Society's effort to reformat their brittle oversize negatives; most of the negatives from which these prints were made have been destroyed.
  The photographs in this series are arranged into the following subseries, alphabetically by subject: Bridge and River Views; Churches; Commercial and Public Buildings; Hotels; Restaurants; Street Scenes; Theaters; and Miscellaneous. Within each series, photographs are arranged alphabetically. Corresponding negative numbers have been written in parentheses after each subject to aid researchers and indicate the number of views available. Many of Roege's views are populated by active people and early automobiles, and provide an energetic glimpse of city life from the 1910s through 1930s.
  - Bridge and River Views
    - Brooklyn Bridge and Manhattan from Brooklyn Heights, [1915], 1924 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
      General note
      (9305, 9306, 9307, 9378)
    - East River and New York from Brooklyn Heights, [1915] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
      2 part panorama: 9303, 9304
    - East River and South Street, 1932 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
      (9309)
    - Hudson River, towards New Jersey from Woolworth Tower, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
      (9302)
    - Hudson River and downtown New York from New Jersey, [1922-1925] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
      (9336)
    - Hudson River and midtown New York from New Jersey, 1931 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
  - Churches
    - St. Bartholomew's Church, [1921] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
      (9385)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral, 1934-1935, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
      (9413, 9414 - 2 copies)
  - Commercial and Public Buildings
    - American Museum of Natural History, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
      (9474)
    - American Seaman's Friend Societys Institute, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
      (9334)
    - City Hall and Municipal Building Tower, 1923 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
      (9325)
    - Federal Hall, with United States Food Administration food drive sign, 1918 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
      (9314)
    - Long Island Warehouse and Storage, Brooklyn, 1917 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
      (9496)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1924 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
      (9492)
    - New York Public Library, 1923 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
      (9396)
    - Pennsylvania Station, Seventh Avenue, 1923 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
      (9368, 9369)
    - Tammany Hall, with Olympic Burlesque, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
      (9344)
    - White Rats Club, 1914 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
      (9436)
  - Hotels
    - Hotel Aberdeen, 1918 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (9390)
    - Hotel Albert, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (9342)
    - Hotel Anderson, 1918 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (9475)
    - The Annex Hotel, 1918 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (9360, 9361, 9362)
    - Hotel Belleclaire, 1914 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (Boyette)(9473 - 2 copies)
    - The Breslin Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (9356)
    - Brevoort Hotel, [1910], 1919 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (9338, 9339)
    - Buckingham Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      (9410)
    - Hotel Claman for Men, 1923 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      (9428)
    - Claremont Inn, including Grant's Tomb, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      (9481)
    - Hotel Claridge, 1919 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      (Boyette)(9433)
    - Collingwood Hotel, 1914 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      (9391)
    - Commodore Hotel, [1928] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      (9379)
    - Hotel Cumberland, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      (9449)
    - Hotel De France, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      (9446)
    - Hotel Endicott, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
    - Hotel Ennis, 1915 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
      (9381)
    - Hotel Flanders, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
      (9440, 9441)
    - Hotel Gonfarone, 1914 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
      (9337)
    - Gramatan Hotel - Bronxville, New York, 1916 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
      (9498)
    - Grand Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
      (9357)
    - Great Northern Hotel, 1910 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
      (9459)
    - Hotel Hargrave, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
      (9471)
    - Hotel Hermitage, includes Stanley Theatre, [1915] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
      (9427)
    - Lafayette Place Hotel, 1910 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (9335)
    - Hotel Lenox, 1916 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (9434)
    - Hotel Longacre with King Edward Hotel, [1910-1919] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (Boyette)(9439)
    - Hotel Lyndemon, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (9451)
    - Hotel Marie Antoinette (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (Boyette)(9469)
    - Hotel Markwell, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (9444)
    - Hotel Martha Washington, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (9355)
    - The Mohawk, Brooklyn, 1917 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (9495)
    - Murray Hill Hotel, with Belmont Hotel and Grand Central Terminal, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
      (9376)
    - National Hotel, 1915 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
      (9333)
    - Hotel Navarre, 1910, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
      (9372, 9373)
    - New Weston Hotel, 1914 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
      (9383)
    - Hotel Richmond, [1915] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
      (9402)
    - Hotel St. Andrew, [1916] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
      (9472)
    - Hotel St. James, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
      (9435)
    - St. Regis Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
      (9418)
    - Union Square Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
      (9346)
    - Wentworth Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
      (9403)
    - Hotel Woodbury, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
      (9452)
    - Hotel Woodstock, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
      (9431)
  - Restaurants
    - Browne's Chop House, includes Empire Theatre, Broadway and 40th Street, 1913 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
      (9425)
    - Cafe Lafayette, University Place at East 9th Street, [1916] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
      (9340)
    - Child's Restaurant and Hong Kong Low, 21-27 Park Row, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
      (Boyette)(9326)
    - Guffanti's Restaurant, Seventh Avenue between 25th and 26th Streets, 1918, [1920] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
      (Boyette)(9365, 9366)
    - Alt Heidelberg Restaurant and Tavern, 130-132 Third Avenue, 1914 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
      (9345)
    - Keene's Chop House, 72 West 36th Street, 1917 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
      (9364)
    - Lion D'Or, 61-57 West 24th Street, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
      (9348)
    - Lussier Restaurant, West 43rd Street, 1916 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
      (9429, 9430)
    - Nassau Cafe and Restaurant, Seventh Avenue and 32nd Street, [1916] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
      (9371)
    - Stark's Restaurant, Reade and Lafayette Streets, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
      (9324)
    - Zum Brau Haus, 205-211 East 54th Street, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
      (9448)
  - Street Scenes - Named Streets and Avenues
    - Beekman Street, 127-137, Blackfords, [1916] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
      (9316)
    - Bowling Green and Broadway, 1921, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
      (9317, 9318)
    - Bridge Street from Whitehall Street, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
      (9310)
    - Broad Street, 30-60, 1918 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
      (9312)
    - Broad Street, south from Wall Street including the New York Stock Exchange Building, 1923 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
      (9311)
    - Broadway from Battery north to 32nd Street, 1919-1923, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 16)
      9319, 9320, 9322, 9323, 9350, 9358)
    - Broadway at Seventh Avenue and from 42nd - 45th Streets [Times Square], 1912, 1923 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 17)
      (9426, 9437 - 3 copies)
    - Broadway from 54th to 130th Streets, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 18)
      (9450, 9482, 9478)
    - Bryant Park, looking east toward Fifth Avenue, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
      (9393)
    - Canal Street, looking east across Sullivan and Thompson Streets, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
      (9332)
    - Central Park, rooftop view from West 60th Street, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
      (9466)
    - Central Park West, looking north from 62nd Street, 1913 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
      (9467)
    - Chatham Square, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
      (9329, 9330)
    - Doyers Street at Bowery, [1915] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
      (9331)
    - Lexington Avenue at East 53rd Street, Y.W.C.A., undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
      (9386)
    - Madison Avenue at 35th Street, 1918 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
      (9375)
    - Park Row, looking West from Chatham Square, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
      (9328)
    - Pearl and William Streets, looking toward Park Row, 1915 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
      (9327)
    - Pine Street, 70-78, 1922 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
      (9315)
    - Riverside Drive, 524-547, [1912] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
      (Boyette) (9480)
    - Union Square, Navy Recruiting Station, [1917-1918] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
      (9347)
  - Street Scenes - Numbered Avenues
    - Fifth Avenue at 38th - 47th Streets, 1923-1924, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 21)
      (9392, 9394, 9395, 9398, 9399, 9405)
    - Fifth Avenue at 48th - 54th Streets, includes Vanderbilt Houses and St. Patrick's Cathedral, 1923-1924, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 22)
      (9407-2 copies, 9408, 9411, 9412, 9409, 9416, 9417)
    - Fifth Avenue from 55th to 59th Streets, [1920-1923], undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 23)
      (9418, 9419 - 2 copies, 9421 - 3 copies, 9422 - 2 copies)
    - Seventh Avenue from 31st to 56th Street, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 24)
      (9367, 9374, 9455)
  - Street Scenes - Numbered Streets
    - West 22nd Street, South side, east of Seventh Avenue, 1916 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
      (9351)
    - West 23rd Street, 64-74, 1917 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
      (9352)
    - West 34th Street, including McCreery's, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
      (9389)
    - West 42nd Street, at Sixth Avenue, 1910 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
      (9397)
    - West 43rd Street, 127-139, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
    - West 45th Street, 38-44, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
      (9400)
    - West 46th Street, 41-63, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
    - West 46th Street, 68-74, [1915] (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
    - West 47th Street, snow-covered, looking east from Sixth Avenue, 1929 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
      (9404)
    - East 48th Street, north side looking west from and including Vanderbilt Avenue, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
      (9382)
    - East 49th Street, 31-51, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
      (9384)
    - West 55th Street, rooftop view to west, 1923 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
      (9457)
    - West 59th Street, rooftop view looking northwest toward Eighth and Ninth Avenues, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
    - West 57th Street, looking west across Seventh Avenue, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
    - West 72nd Street, 104-118, 1924 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
      (9470)
    - West 102nd Street, rooftop view across West End Avenue to the Hudson River and New Jersey, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
      (Boyette)(9479)
  - Theaters
    - Cort, 1914 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 27)
      (9442)
    - Olympic Burlesque, 1914 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 27)
      (9343)
    - The Plaza, Brooklyn, 1917 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 27)
      (9493)
    - Shubert Theatre, 1917 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 27)
      (9432)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Charter of Elks Lodge, New York, 1871, copy, undated (Offsite-box 2, Folder 28)
      (9300)
- Series II: Negatives
  Series II spans the period from ca. 1912 to 1937 and includes both film and glass negatives varying in size from 4 x 5 to 11 x 14 inches. Negatives are arranged according to format and size, and thereunder by negative numbers assigned by The New-York Historical Society. Upon accession, staff assigned numbers between 9001 and 9499 to Roege's negatives which were arranged first by size and thereunder very loosely by geographic location. This order may reflect Roege's own filing system.
  Oversize negatives in this collection were once part of the George P. Hall & Son Photograph Collection, and were assigned new negative numbers beginning with 666 and with a -D suffix (which was used to indicate oversize negatives) for inclusion in the Negative Collection card catalog. These numbers are still listed on the negative enclosures and are given in parentheses after image descriptions within this finding aid. Where there are gaps in the negative numbering, the negatives were not present at the time of processing and are presumed to have been destroyed.
  Hotels, street scenes, rooftop views, and churches in Manhattan are well represented, and are joined by a large group of photographs of Columbia University and other institutions, primarily in Manhattan. A few images of business districts in the Bronx, the New Jersey waterfront, and other locations near Manhattan are included. Although many of Roege's views consist of systematic documentation of businesses, probably done on commission, he also turned his camera to less commonly photographed sites including saloons on Chatham Square in the Bowery, and German ocean liners interned in New Jersey during World War I. Images also include those of Temple Emanu-El and Rockefeller Center soon after they were constructed.
  - Film Negatives - 4 x 5 inches
    - Rockefeller Center [Radio City], ice-skating and architectural details, 1937 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9001-9005)
  - Film Negatives - 5 x 7 inches
    - Hamburg-American Packet Co., 1908 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9006)
    - Hudson River and New York skyline from Park Place to Morris Street, [1926] (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9007)
    - Nassau Street, aerial view, west side from Wall to Cedar Streets, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9008)
      [Copy negative of a halftone, ca. 1902]
    - Wall Street, west from and including New Street, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9009)
      [Copy negative of a photograph by Underhill, ca. 1911]
    - Union Nominations, broadside listing candidates for 1864 election, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9010)
      [Copy negative of a ca. 1864 broadside]
    - Whyte's Restaurant, Fulton Street, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9011)
      [Copy negative of a 1914 original]
    - Wall Street, Federal Hall, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9012)
      [Copy negative of a 1916 original]
    - Seventh Avenue, west side from 39th Street, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9013)
      [Copy negative of a ca. 1928 original]
    - Seventh Avenue, Times Building, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9014)
      [Copy negative of 1916 original]
    - Broadway at Times Square, looking south, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9015)
      [Copy negative of a 1915 original]
    - 42nd Street, looking west from Third Avenue, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9016)
      [Copy negative of a 1924 original]
    - Broadway, 2787-2797, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9017)
      [Copy negative of a Mar. 1916 original]
    - Unidentified apartment house, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9018)
      (Boyette)[Copy negative]
    - Columbia University Views, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9022-9042)
      [Copy negatives of 1915 originals]
    - St. Paul's Cathedral, interior, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9043)
      [Copy negative of 1915 original]
    - Columbia University Views, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9044-9046)
    - City Hall Park and U.S. Post Office, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9047)
    - Fulton Street, east from Gold Street, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9048)
    - Fifth Avenue, north from 25th Street, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9049)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral, Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9050)
    - Sixth Avenue and 39th Street, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9051)
    - Sixth Avenue and 40th Street, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9052)
    - Hippodrome, Sixth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9053)
    - Sixth Avenue, looking north from 44th to 48th Streets, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9054-9056)
    - Eighth Avenue, from 31st to 56th Streets, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9057-9061)
    - Broadway from 18th to 41st Streets, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9062-9065)
    - East 21st Street, north side, 145-159, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9066)
    - West 23rd Street, north side, from Eighth to Seventh Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9067)
    - West 42nd Street, from Fifth to Twelfth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9068-9071)
    - West 77th Street, north side west from Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9072)
    - West 45th Street, looking west from Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9073)
    - West 46th Street, looking east from Sixth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9074)
    - West 46th Street, north side west from Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9075)
    - West 47th Street, looking east from Sixth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9076)
    - West 47th Street, north side west from Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9077)
    - West 48th Street, looking west in front of 220-228, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9078)
    - West 50th Street, looking west on north side from no. 13, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9079)
    - West 51st Street, looking west from Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9080)
    - West 53rd Street, looking west from no. 7, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9081)
    - West 54th Street, north side west from Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9082)
    - West 56th Street, west from just west of Fifth Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9083)
    - East 56th Street, west from Third Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9084)
    - East 57th Street, north side, west of Third Avenue, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9085)
    - West 59th Street and Columbus Circle, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9086)
  - Film Negatives - 8 x 10 inches
    - Belvidere Clubhouse, Cherry Street, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9087)
      [Copy negative of a print, ca. 1795]
    - Broadway, west side between 78th and 79th Streets, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9088)
      [Copy negative of a print]
    - Chambers Street, 39-43, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9089)
      [Copy negative of a lithograph, ca. 1827]
    - W.O.R. Broadcasting Station, Newark, New Jersey, 1934 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9090)
      See: Box 5